https://www.contextures.com/privacy.html

Thank you for visiting
the Contextures website, owned by Contextures Inc., which is located in Canada. The site is hosted on servers owned by SiteGround, which is located in the UK. We respect and protect the privacy of our users. This
privacy policy tells you how we collect and use information.
The term "Personal Information" in this privacy policy means any
information from which your identity is apparent or can be reasonably
ascertained. We do not collect Personal Information about you when you
visit this online service.
Scope
The purpose of this website is to provide you with trusted
information about using Microsoft Excel.
Personal information
If you contact us we will collect the email address, and
any other identifying information you provide, such as a name or phone
number. Please do not give us other personal or sensitive information.
Website analytics
This site does not collect any data from visitors, other than standard server
logs. However, to improve your experience on our site, we may use 'cookies' -- a cookie is
a small text file that a site may place on your computer as a tool to
remember your preferences. Cookies
are an industry standard and most major web sites use them.
You may refuse the use of cookies by
selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note
that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of
this website.
Our website may contain links to other websites. Please note that
we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites, so when you go to other websites from here,
be aware and
read their privacy policy.
Our website uses Google Analytics, a service which transmits website
traffic data to Google servers in the United States. Google Analytics
does not identify individual users or associate your IP address with any
other data held by Google. We use reports provided by Google Analytics
to help us understand website traffic and webpage usage.
By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner described in Google's Privacy Policy and for the purposes set out above. You can opt out of Google Analytics if you disable or refuse the cookie, disable JavaScript, or use the opt-out service provided by Google.
Advertising
This Site is affiliated with CMI Marketing, Inc., d/b/a CafeMedia ("CafeMedia") for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site, and CafeMedia will collect and use certain data for advertising purposes. To learn more about CafeMedia's data usage, click here
www.cafemedia.com/publisher-advertising-privacy-policy
Also, this site does use third-party advertising companies, including
Google and Amazon, to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies
may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone
number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements
about goods and services of interest to you.
These advertisers may use cookies which are collected by the advertising
companies. For more information about this practice and to know your choices
about not having this information used by these companies, please check the
advertisers' websites for respective privacy policies.
Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to this website or other websites.
Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve
ads to your users based on their visit to this site, and/or other sites
on the Internet.
You may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting Google's Ads Settings, or by visiting the About Ads opt out page.
Subscriptions
If you sign up for my Excel newsletter, your name and email address are collected, and securely stored, by AWeber. You can use the link at the bottom of any email, to immediately unsubscribe from the mailing list. Emails will no longer be sent to you, and your information will be deleted from the mailing list.
If you purchase Contextures' Excel products, the transaction is managed through the secure e-junkie.com website. The payment is processed through PayPal, and they do not share your credit card details with me, or with e-junkie. PayPal only notifies us that your payment has been completed, so that the product can be sent to you., and product support can be provided, if required
If you subscribe to my RSS Feeds or Email Updates (powered by Feedburner),
I ask for contact information such as name and email address. You may opt-out
of these communications at any time. Your personal information will never
be sold or given to a third party, and you will never be spammed by me.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns please contact Debra Dalgleish at ddalgleish @ contextures.com
Privacy policy dated September 2020.
